{
    "subject": "resource/List_of_Jo_Stafford_compilation_albums_(1955\u201399)",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Philips_Records",
    "human_readable": "The label of List of Jo Stafford compilation albums (1955\u201399) is Philips Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8520317673683167,
            "question": "What record label released the compilation albums of Jo Stafford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8301399350166321,
            "question": "What is the name of the label that released Jo Stafford's compilation albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8036673069000244,
            "question": "Can you name a specific compilation album by Jo Stafford released by Philips Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6961370706558228,
            "question": "During what years were Jo Stafford's compilation albums released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506403088569641,
            "question": "What type of media are Jo Stafford's compilation albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6027750968933105,
            "question": "How many compilation albums did Jo Stafford release in total?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47615984082221985,
            "question": "Who is Jo Stafford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42113807797431946,
            "question": "What genre of music is Jo Stafford known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3120044469833374,
            "question": "Is Philips Records still in operation today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28823935985565186,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations on these compilation albums?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of List of Jo Stafford compilation albums (1955\u201399) is Philips Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3703_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Philips Records still in operation today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3703_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Jo Stafford known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3703_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Jo Stafford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3703_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3703_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information contains a compilation album released by Philips Records in 1955, titled \"The Voice of Your Choice\", but the fact statement only specifies a single label for all Jo Stafford's compilation albums from 1955 to 1999.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}